# **Austin Baxley**

🗣 Atlanta, Georgia, United States 🗳 AusBaxley@gmail.com 🚨 678-435-3558 🛅 in/abaxley2 🛎 https://github.com/abaxley2

## **SUMMARY**

Full Stack Developer with experience in designing, maintaining, and building websites and web applications. I specialize in JavaScript and have experience with using MySQL, NoSQL, Node.js, and React. Also experienced with MongoDB, Express, and Handlebars.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Restaurant Manager**

Tin Lizzy's Cantina

January 2020 - May 2021, Kennesaw, GA

- · Launched new product offerings.
- · Managed a large and intricate inventory of product and ordered product to fill any gaps.
- · Managed a large and diverse team and wrote all scheduling.

#### **Band Director**

**Cobb County Schools** 

September 2013 - May 2016, Marietta, GA

- · Developed curriculum and conducted clinics to enable students to learn in an adaptable setting.
- Performed and organized at over 40 performances including concerts, festivals, and parades.
- · Instructed and maintained a group of over 400 students each year.

# **Restaurant Manager**

CentraArchy Restaurant Management Group

March 2013 - December 2019, Atlanta, GA

- · Sourced, developed, and trained new restaurant managers.
- · Increased key metrics including guest counts, revenue per guest.
- · Increased overall revenue by 15%.

## **PROJECTS**

## **Regex Tutorial**

Georgia Tech Coding Bootcamp · August 2021

- · Developed a working tutorial on Regular Expressions.
- · Explained in detail each aspect of Regex and it's applicable use.
- · Successfully deployed a GitHub Gist.
- · GitHub Gist: https://gist.github.com/abaxley2/a796040212cdac792dc67c286ba42a41

## **Get Money Smart**

Georgia Tech Coding Bootcamp • July 2021

- $\cdot \ Created\ a\ mobile-responsive\ banking\ web\ application\ as\ a\ tool\ for\ teachers.$
- · Created and tested API routes.
- · Successfully deployed application to Heroku.
- $\cdot \ GitHub\ Link: \ https://github.com/mlward639/Get\_Money\_Smart$
- · Deployed Link: https://polar-river-76787.herokuapp.com/

### **Market Finder**

Georgia Tech Coding Bootcamp  $\cdot$  June 2021

- · Created a web application that used third party APIs to locate local farmer's markets by location.
- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$  Wrote and managed project assignments.
- · Successfully deployed the application through GitHub.
- · GitHub Link: https://github.com/abaxley2/Market-Finder
- · Deployed Link: https://abaxley2.github.io/Market-Finder/

#### **EDUCATION**

## Bachelor's of Music in Music Education

Kennesaw State University · Kennesaw, GA · 2012

#### **SKILLS**

 $Technical \, Skills: \, Html, \, Css, \, Javascript, \, Jquery, \, Nodejs, \, React \, Js, \, Node \, Jsexperience, \, Bootstrap, \, Express, \, Mongoose, \, Graphql \, Apollo, \, MVC, \, Webapi, \, Mongo \, Db, \, Nosql, \, MySQL \,$